<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE html>
<html xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<head>
  <title>Game Mania</title>
  <link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="styles.css" />
</head>
<body>
  <div id="container">
    <h1>Game Mania</h1>

    <game-review>
      <h2>Red Dead Redemption 2 (RDR2)</h2>
      <game-info>
        <img src="rdr2.jpg" alt="Red Dead Redemption 2" class="small-image"/>
        <p>Red Dead Redemption 2 is an action-adventure game set in the American Wild West....</p>
      </game-info>
      <game-rating>
        <h3>Overall Rating: 4.8 stars</h3>
        <p>User Reviews:</p>
        <user-review>
          <h4>Saul Goodman</h4>
          <p>Amazing game with stunning graphics and immersive storyline!</p>
          <span>5 stars</span>
        </user-review>
      </game-rating>
    </game-review>
    
    <game-review>
      <h2>Grand Theft Auto V (GTA V)</h2>
      <game-info>
        <img src="gtav.jpg" alt="Grand theft auto" class="small-image"/>
        <p>Grand Theft Auto V is an action-adventure game played from either a third-person or first-person perspective. 
        	Players complete missions—linear scenarios with set objectives—to progress through the story. 
        	Outside of the missions, players may freely roam the open world</p>
      </game-info>
      <game-rating>
        <h3>Overall Rating: 4.4 stars</h3>
        <p>User Reviews:</p>
        <user-review>
          <h4>Gustavo Fring</h4>
          <p>Rating: 5/5 I recently immersed myself in the vast and dynamic world of Grand Theft Auto V,
          	 and I must say it's an absolute masterpiece! Rockstar Games has truly outdone themselves with this one.
          	 The open-world of Los Santos is nothing short of breathtaking.
          	  The attention to detail is incredible, from the bustling city streets to the serene landscapes.
          	  Every corner feels alive, and the level of immersion is unparalleled.
          	  The storyline is gripping, with three distinct protagonists whose lives intertwine in unexpected ways. 
          	  The character development is top-notch, making it easy to connect with each of them. The missions are diverse, 
          	  ranging from high-speed chases to intricate heists, keeping the gameplay fresh and exciting.</p>
          <span>5 stars</span>
        </user-review>
      </game-rating>
    </game-review>
    
    <game-review>
      <h2>Ghost of Tsushima</h2>
      <game-info>
        <img src="ghost.jpg" alt="Ghost of Tsushima" class="small-image"/>
        <p>This is an action game in which players assume the role of a samurai (Jin Sakai) 
        	on a quest for vengeance against Mongol invaders in 13th century Japan. Players traverse open-world environments, 
        	interact with characters, complete quests (e.g., assassination), and infiltrate enemy strongholds.</p>
      </game-info>
      <game-rating>
        <h3>Overall Rating: 4.8 stars</h3>
        <p>User Reviews:</p>
        <user-review>
          <h4>Smanga Simelane</h4>
          <p>OMG what an incredible game!!!! I'm about fifteen hours in and GoS is an epic of an adventure. 
          	It's the feudal Japan game we've been begging for for years!
          	I always thought Ubisoft would deliver an AC game set in ancient Japan but Sony and SP took up that gauntlet 
          	and delivered a gaming experience Ubi could only dream of making!</p>
          <span>5 stars</span>
        </user-review>
      </game-rating>
    </game-review>
    
    <game-review>
      <h2>Assassin's Creed Mirage</h2>
      <game-info>
        <img src="creed.jpg" alt="Assassin's Creed Mirage" class="small-image"/>
        <p>In this smaller scale, back to basics Assassin's caper, you play Basim, a young street thief seeking answers. 
        	Roam the richly-detailed, reactive and vibrant streets of 9th century Baghdad, uncovering the mysteries of the past as you fight to secure your future.</p>
      </game-info>
      <game-rating>
        <h3>Overall Rating: 2.8 stars</h3>
        <p>User Reviews:</p>
        <user-review>
          <h4>Tyler “Grim” </h4>
          <p>This game was a major set back from the AC games before. Don't waist the money. I'm a huge AC fan but this was a HUGE disappointment in my opinion. 
          	Mirage should have been a separate series or its own story not a carry over of the AC franchise. </p>
          <span>1 stars</span>
        </user-review>
      </game-rating>
    </game-review>



  </div>
</body>
</html>
